Anand sh Italy hard work home nahi b tube
light
[music]
lag le ae jane please welcome act of night
Mr Manan
Desai
today I start the show first on you one promise my
right ready show hand fire let's go I am a
resident of Mumbai today take a promise
Manan Desai who many times on stage
kaise naath khootu did not feel wrong I did not feel wrong
thanks
just take a promise but no
one stopped him from
coming again nice a little dilemma
lagi 00 yours take Manan name animal lo
500 300
waane okhe manan name
animal
nala
oh b v your information yourselves you are
not spoiling your backside bagla
la ma
ba straight head talk today
we have a lot of
laughter
tonda de
simple today comedy vulgar community has licked
the comedian community has only triggered
loss to dice  I'm not a
fan of traditional cuisine
I'm talking about my daughter ...
but I felt bad, I am
sorry, I am not feeling bad, I am thankful, if I am doing this then I feel bad, if I am celebrating a
birthday then it feels bad, my
mother is Shri Krishna then I felt bad, that
day the beggar has a big form, you go to my house, my
name is Deep Bhai, I am from Newa Ma, I felt bad, I felt bad, a
few days ago there was
a birthday party, so I came to Dhyana, my
Dikri, seven years old, I am
lying on the ground with glitter, I am a cultured person, please wash my
Gujarati
father, I am Mari Dikri, I am a big man in English, these
days I have to wash my
Gujarati father, you are not in English, Dhyana, don't do that, your hands are getting dirty, please get up, take your hands, don't say Gujarati,
rest I am towards my wife, I am my wife
Vidya, I am just for two minutes, please take out my
Gujarati paper, Papa, I will
also come inside, Papa Vidya,
ok, I am lying on the ground like a gutter
Sorry Papa Sorry Sorry
Bane The Trauma Pade Mein Trauma Mein To
Jeevan
Pragati Na Jo Maan Dari Walen Dariyo Barabar Mari Dari Se Atak
Dariyo I To Naki Kar K Agar To
Pub Dara
Haramkhor J Mar Dene Ra Scene Jone Ek Do
Pop
Out Ek Do Kas Kas
Santa Bin Ne Ne Ne Unsolicited Advice
You are young people have different life
experiences your experiences are different Chhata I have come immediately Papa no
no mind
please no today you are not umar rani so
what do you want to do
ek minute and baak disrespect kar
desh mummy vas sa beta ek to jane mummy i mean
parent advice to me I
feel sometime r on pen pal wast person to give
you pen pal advice especially rest of the
mummy
project chal aur baaki 3 varsha bharo
chaul
project mere singing sakh to Ajit Singh paase jaan
na Pooja paase thodi
[Music]
[Prashant]